carmencitta.me 2018-03-09

# Privacy Policy - Carmencitta Magazine

Carmencitta is committed to the privacy of individuals who visit and interact with **[www.carmencitta.me](http://www.carmencitta.me/).** This statement discloses the privacy practices for this website. It applies to all Carmencitta websites – that is all sites within the “Carmencitta” domain name.

This Privacy Policy explains how Carmencitta handles all your personal information and data. By accessing this website, you are accepting the practices described in this statement.

**Collecting Log Files**

Like most standard web servers, this website uses log files. These files contain information such as Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), the time spent online, along with other similar data. This is not linked to any personally identifiable information and is used to statistical analysis of website traffic only.

This website also uses cookies. The user is always free to decline our cookies if his/her browser permits. However, by setting a cookie, Carmencitta will remember the used the next time he/she visits it. Cookies shall only be used to obtain non-personal information to improve your online experience.

**Collecting Personal Information**

There are instances where Carmencitta requests personally identifiable information. These include but are not limited to a name, mailing address, and possibly additional sensitive information. These are solely used to provide you with specific services or correspondence.

**Sharing Personal Information**

Carmencitta reserves the right to share some of your personally identifiable information with our affiliated services partners. These include but are not limited to our customer support and transactions processing partners. They will only obtain the personal information needed to deliver the service in provision to you.

**Sharing Information with Third Parties**

Carmencitta websites contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices used by other websites. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website.

**Notification of Changes**

Carmencitta reserves the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time. These changes will be posted to this page. Your continued use of the website after such change is made is considered acceptance of and agreement to be bound by the terms of the Privacy Policy as modified.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions or concerns about Carmencitta Privacy Policy, please contact us on: info@carmencitta.me .
